techdealdigger.com 2014-02-10

# TechDealDigger

TechDealDigger is serious about protecting your online privacy. This Privacy Statement explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as a user of our system.

"You" or "Your" means you as a participant in or as a user of TechDealDigger.com . "We" or "Our" or "Us" means TechDealDigger.com . "Our site" means TechDealDigger.com .

Section 1. Collected Information  
We may automatically collect and/or track the following:

  1. web page http headers (home server domain names, IP address, type of client computer, and type of Web browser);
  2. information knowingly provided by you through on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and or other entries, such as email addresses, personal, financial or demographic information;
  3. information, user specific or aggregate, on what pages our visitors access and
  4. the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with TechDealDigger.com via e-mail.

Section 2. Use of Data Collected  
We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience at our site, enabling us to present content we think you might be interested in.  We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site, for marketing and promotional purposes, for statistical analysis, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online.

Section 3. Disclosure of Data to Third Parties  
We will only disclose your personal information to third parties information with your prior explicit permission.   We reserve the right to disclose aggregate demographic and profile data to third parties.   
This site contains links to other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

Section 4. Your Opt-Out Rights  
You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and or our partners when we request your information. We also allow you to remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database, it will no longer be used by us for any purpose.  You can remove your information by writing to us via postal mail at the address below.

Section 5. Your Rights To Your Personal Data  
Upon request via postal mail or e-mail, we will provide you a summary of personal information retained by us. We will only send your personal records to your e-mail address or postal address we have on file for you. You may modify, correct, change, or update your personal record or remove your personal record from our database by contacting TechDealDigger.com via postal mail at the address below, or via the Customer Inquiry form.

Section 6. We Do Not Intend To Collect Data From Children  
The information and services provided us or our affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children (under 18 years old). No information collected from children is knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside TechDealDigger.com .

Section 7. Our Right To Contact You  
We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you.

Section 8. Redirects  
Note that when you click on a coupon link, you will be directed to the advertiser's website.

Section 9. Our Right To Change  
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our site.   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us online using our contact form or write to: 

TechDealDigger – Incline Interactive LLC  
PO Box 6659  
Incline Village, NV 89450
